<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ambassador</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bottom">Bottom</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="notification_error_ssl_cert_invalid">Invalide ssl</string>

    <string name="prayer"> A scriptural definition, states that faith is the connecting power into the spiritual realm,
        this power which I believe is the “Holy Spirit”, the Spirit of God that abides within us, this power links us
        with God and makes Him a  tangible, able to be experiences through the 5 senses, a tangible reality of a person.
    </string>
    <string name="prayer1">
        Hebrews 11:1-3 (NIV) states, Now faith is the confidence inn what we hope for and assurance about what we do not see.
        2. This is what the ancients were commended for.
        3. By Faith we understand that the universe was formed at God’s
        command, so that what is seen was not made our of what was visible.
</string>
    <string name="prayer2">
        Faith is so important that the bible tells us that without Faith, it is impossible to please God, because anyone
        who comes to God must first believe that he exists and believe that God will reward those who earnestly seek Him.
        (paraphrased Hebrews 11:6).</string>

    <string name="education"> It is said that the purpose or the aim of education is to evolve or grow and change people into
        productive citizens from childhood and beyond.
    </string>

    <string name="education1"> As productive citizens we are then expected to use the knowledge gained, our talents, and
        learned skills to sustain ourselves and help others while pushing the human race forward in equality, equity, and harmony.  I still believe that education is key!
    </string>

    <string name="education2"> Hosea 4:6a (KJV) states My people are destroyed for lack of knowledge:
    </string>

    <string name="mens">
    “Manna Nuggets”  MEN WITH MANNA- is  15 minutes of  impromptu expressions from various men of God and Ambassador Sheila
    Renee to minister, encourage , motivate Men to pray. When Men Pray…
</string>

    <string name="featuredbusiness">
  Featured Small Business-ENTREPRENEUR of the Week. A weekly showcase/quarterly parade of entrepreneurship.

</string>

    <string name="faith">
Remember, The Choice is Your! What choice, Every Choice!

</string>


    <string name="community"> According to Tim Stafford, “The Justice Conference bible”, When Justice is done, it generally
        begins with a community of people who first learn how to act justly and then apply the lesson outward.  Being a
        Human Relations, Social Justice Major myself, I am an advocate for equality understanding it does not mean “the same”,
        fairness and equal playing field and thus, I shall continue to fight for those who may not be able to verbally speak
        for themselves and those who afraid to speak or those who do not have my boldness I shall, I will SPEAK for Social
        Justice and equality producing  level ground.
    </string>

    <string name="community1"> Deuteronomy 32:4 (KJV) He is the Rock, his work is perfect: for all his ways are judgement:
        a God of truth and without iniquity, just and right is he
    </string>

    <string name="symbis">You want the very best for the couple in your care and you want a system that make it
        personal, profound and easy.SYMBIS has been an incredible tool to help couple preparefor the most
        important decision of their life. She encourages you to ask the hard questions and
        truly dig into being more prepared for marriage.</string>


    <string name="financial">To be financially literate is to know how to handle your currency. This means
        learning how to pay your bill, how to borrow and save money responsibly, and how and why to invest
        and plan for retirement. She helps you to manage money. She gives Personal finance experts advise.
    </string>


    <string name="credit">
        Our company helps to increase your credit score making you more creditworthy to make large purchases
        or small purchases like homes, automobiles, get loans for college and other purchases. Also, we help
        you to dispute falsely reported items in your credit report. And we also educate, so you can continue
        to keep your credit score up and we monitor your credit report.
    </string>



    <string name="speaking">At Ambassador Sheila Renee, we think of each presentation as a three-legged stool,
        supported by content, design, and delivery. Delivery has a vast impact on how an audience hear your message,
        and poor delivery can leave your presentation feeling…a little off. What you say matter; how you say it
        matter just as much. Ambassador Sheila Renee’s approach to speaker coaching drives clients towards a
        delivery style that’s comfortable, dynamic, and empathetic. Our inside-out approach to coaching address
        both outside behaviors and their causal causes. We’ll help you discover core strengths, develop traits
        of the world’s most captivating speakers, and become your own unique brand of the powerful presenter.
    </string>

    <string name="teach">Ambassador Sheila Renee is a Motivational Speaker, Life Coach. She is Counseling
        /Coaching people. she has helped many people to understand their personal and professional-strength
        and help them to identify their week area and improve them. This is an general themed format with
        one individual goal in mind: to move your audience. It is designed to energize the audience and
        get them inspired toward a goal that acting a role in their position, life or both. Many time
        organization utilize the term seminar and workshop interchangeably. In reality, seminar are
        designed for the audience to learn through the presenter, with incomplete audience participation.
    </string>

    <string name="motivational">There are lots of motivational business speakers to pick from but Ambassador Sheila
        Renee’s story is quite different than the rest. She knows firsthand on overcoming extreme obstacles and how
        to turn stumbling blocks into stepping stones. She has inspired many audiences to develop their mental
        toughness muscle as well as their courage and patience muscle. Ambassador Sheila Renee’s business keynotes
        are based on true life experiences that have turned trials into triumphs. As an inspiring business speaker,
        Ambassador Sheila Renee has encouraged thousands of employees to develop the mental strength to overcome
        adversity and excuses. Her keynote speeches aim to cultivate focus, ambition, and accountability.
    </string>

    <string name="groupfac">A group facilitator is someone who helps a group of people understand their common
        objectives and goals and assists them to plan how to achieve them; in doing so, it is key that the
        facilitator remains “neutral” meaning he/she does not take a particular position in the discussion.
        Sometimes the facilitator might need to step into a training role during the session to facilitate
        discussion. In the context of group facilitation, all opinions count and the facilitator’s role is
        to encourage all voices to be heard. Ambassador Sheila Renee has extensive experience as a group
        facilitator with diverse audiences. Her aim is to make sure the group opens up to share information
        in a safe and organic manner where all opinions count no matter how sensitive the subject of discussion
        is. Examples of her work include group facilitation on Confidence building, Corporate Values, Creative
        Brainstorming, Performance management and more.
    </string>

    <string name="pastor">Worship leaders not only help maintain the church culture, but they also help shape it.
        Worship itself is a holy unity with God that nothing else on this earth quite equals. Yet each worship
        service can be so dissimilar from each other depending on musical choice that the worship leader make.
        Because the church is always change with new people coming in, and others exit, it is never in a static,
        fixed state. If the leaders want to modify the vision of the church, the worship leaders help effect that
        change by adjust their worship leading accordingly.
    </string>

    <string name="business">Business consultant, also recognized as management analyst, work in area that include
        marketing, human resources, management, and accounting. Consultant help improve company by assessing
        weakness and recommending solution. Business consultant provide management consulting to help
        organization improve their performance and effectiveness. These professional analyze business
        and create solution while also helping company meet their goals.
    </string>

    <string name="marketing">A marketing consultant is an outside advisory who works with companies to
        create and implement marketing strategies. A consultant help to create a complete market plan,
        determine a business’s marketing message, and identify the appropriate market mix to get the
        message out to the target market. Most consultant are also involved in implement the marketing
        strategy. They often help monitor results and tweak campaign as they go to ensure that company
        get the best results from their marketing efforts.
    </string>

    <string name="productbrand">Great branding is about giving customers a reason to believe.In this
        competitive marketplace connecting with customers is a priority. If you want them to care
        about your brand you need to do two things; make an emotional connection and create a meaningful
        experience.Our brand consultants helps companies in transforming their brand identities.
    </string>

    <string name="image">Image Consulting is the work of guide, mentoring, educating and supervision
        people on managing their appearance-clothing, grooming, body language and etiquette to create
        positive first impressions to get new opportunity in life and training them on soft skill to
        perform better when these opportunity. Image Consulting is the profession of help people manage
        their image to have a extra rewarding personal, professional, and social life. Image Consultant
        Services for Men, Women, Organizations, Communication Assessment, Appearance Management, Styling,
        Grooming, Personal Shopping and Wardrobe Consulting
    </string>

    <string name="BusinessNetworks">In many situations, having a strong network can bring tremendous benefits.
        If you find yourself unemployed or simply looking to boost your career, networking might actually prove
        to be the most effective tool in ensuring positive results. Our exceptional network speaker will teach
        you how to build and keep strong network, but also why network is very useful for your career or
        company success. If you boost your life or career, we give the Inspirational / Motivational speech.
    </string>

    <string name="SelfEnhancement">Speaker program are geared toward helping each student build brand new
        confidence within him or herself so that the student can be prepared emotionally and psychologically
        for some event that unfolds in their environment. The presentations are also designed to help students
        heighten their awareness of the needs of other students and how their belief and confidence in themselves
        can be transferred to others to help them with their issues and challenges. The programs aim to create
        respect and acceptance of one’s mind, body, and spirit while honoring the same attributes in others.
    </string>

    <string name="Christian">So you’re in charge of finding entertainment for your church’s youth rally, seminar,
        workshop, or another Christ-centered event. Don’t have the equipment for a band and want something a
        tiny more on the serious side than a comedian? Well, then a Christian speaker is just what your event
        wants! There are speaker out there for all age, background, and situation. Whether you want a Christian
        speaker for a senior couples retreat or a workshop for a youth group.Ms. Sheila Renee would help you.
    </string>

    <string name="Conference">Need a top conference speaker for your subsequently corporate event, meeting,
        or conference? Research shows that the best conference speakers can shed invaluable insight into your
        company’s goals, pain points, and focuses. Furthermore, conference speakers are skilled at rallying up
        each unique audience to inspire, engage, empower, and, of course, motivate your team for results such
        as increased productivity, improved employee morale, higher sales, game-changing innovation, or more
        effective communication.
    </string>

    <string name="GroupFacilitator">Ms. Sheila Renee has amazing energy and the ability to connect with audience
        participants, no matter the size or venue. All small group breakouts and workshops include relevant
        customization to align with the distinct needs of the client partner, audience size and time requirements.

Inspirational Seminars for small groups subjects:
Faith, Gods Love, Gods Justice Out of the box Spiritual Detox. God’s Original Intent and Purpose for your life.
        The Way, The weight, and the Wait of God. Lay Aside Every Weight and Finish the RACE.THEY said I wouldn’t
        make it, BUT, WE DID!!!
    </string>

    <string name="Personal">Personal appearance is an often overlooked part of communication and presentation skill.
        When you are speaking in public, you may be instead of your organization or just yourself. It is still
        you at the front. It is you that the new person, group or viewers see and before you have time to open
        your mouth and say everything, positive assumption, both consciously and subconsciously, have been made.
        Ms. Sheila Renee would help you with how to improve Personal appearance.
    </string>



</resources>
